<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
	<string name="appversion">0.4.1</string>

    <!-- Pantalla Login -->
    <string name="app_name">Scores</string>
    <string name="logo">Scores” logo</string>
    <string name="login">Login</string>
    <string name="login_f">Login with Facebook</string>
    <string name="olvida_pass">Forgot your password?</string>
    <string name="registro">Sign up</string>
    <string name="registrate">If you\'re not still a user, Sign up now!</string>
    <string name="slogan">Scores of the future</string>
    <string name="facebook_app_id">1439111256308763</string>
    <string name="beta">Beta</string>
        
   		<!-- Dialogo inicio sesión -->
    	<string name="mail">EMail</string>
    	<string name="pass">Password</string>
    	<string name="login_title">Login</string>
    	<string name="err_campos_vacios">You should to complete all the fields</string>
    	<string name="err_login_unknown_user">User name and/or password incorrect</string>
    	<string name="err_not_active">This account is pending activation</string>
    	<string name="err_login_unknown">There was an error. Please, try again</string>
    	<string name="cancel">Cancel</string>
    	<string name="confirm_login">Login</string>
    	<string name="cerrar_sesion">Logout</string>
    	<string name="close_d">Close</string>
    	<string name="auth">Authenticating&#8230;</string>
    	<string name="err_session">Couldn\'t start the session. Please, try again later.</string>
    	
    	<!-- Dialogo olvido contraseña -->
    	<string name="olvido_title">Recover password</string>
    	<string name="mail_olvido_pass">Introduce Email</string>
    	<string name="confirm_olvidopass">Send</string>
    	<string name="err_olvidopass_unknown">There was an error and could not recover the password.
    	    Please, try again later</string>
    	<string name="olvidopass_ok">We\'ve sent an email with instructions about your password</string>
    	<string name="err_olvidopass_mail">﻿We didn\'t find any account associated with this email</string>
    	<string name="err_olvidopass_mail_not_sent">﻿Your password was changed but couldn\'t send it. 
     Please, try again later</string>
    	
    	<!-- Dialogo registro usuario -->
    	<string name="registro_title">Sign up</string>
    	<string name="nombre_registro">Name</string>
    	<string name="mail_registro">Email</string>
    	<string name="pass_registro">Password</string>
    	<string name="confipass_registro">Confirm password</string>
    	<string name="confirm_registro">Sign up</string>
    	<string name="err_net">﻿There was a network error and it wasn\'t possible to send data. Please, try again later.</string>
    	<string name="err_pass">Passwords don\'t match</string>
    	<string name="err_reg">﻿There was an error trying to do the registration. 
    	    Please, try again later.</string>
    	<string name="err_reg_mail">﻿This email is already in use, please choose another</string>
    	<string name="ok_reg">An email have been sent</string>
    	<string name="ok_reg_mail">﻿Registration is completed but could not send the confirmation email. We\'ll send it manually within a maximum of 24 hours.</string>
    	<string name="creating_account">Creating your account&#8230;</string>
    	<string name="aviso_registro_1">By registering you agree to the </string>
    	<string name="aviso_registro_2">Terms </string>
    	<string name="aviso_registro_3">and </string>
    	<string name="aviso_registro_4">Conditions </string>
    	<string name="aviso_registro_5">of the application</string>
    	
	<!-- Pantalla principal -->
    <string name="titulo_coleccion">My collection</string>
    <string name="bin">Delete</string>
    <string name="action_sort">Sort</string>
    <string name="author">Author</string>
    <string name="author_dialog_title">Select an author</string>
    <string name="instrument">Instrument</string>
    <string name="instrument_dialog_title">Select an instrument</string>
    <string name="name">Sort by name</string>
    <string name="format_dialog_title">Select a format</string>
    <string name="format">Sort by format</string>
    <string name="show_all">Show all</string>
    <string name="action_search">Search</string>
    <string name="no_scores">Your scores collection is empty. 
You can buy scores in our store.</string>
    <string name="no_scores_button">Go to Score Store</string>
    <string name="error_folder">There was a problem iniciating Scores</string>
    <string name="incorrect_security_line">You cannot open this score, is registered by other user</string>
    <string name="incorrect_user">Incorrect user</string>
	<string name="sort_no_scores">There isn\'t Scores to sort</string>
    <string name="sort_error">There was an error in sort</string> 
    <string name="pdf_upload_error">There was an error when uploading the PDF file</string>
    <string name="open_file">Open file</string>       
    <string name="pdf_advise">You should have an external app to open this PDF files </string>
    
    	<!-- Pantalla de subir archivos -->
    	<string name="upload_pdf">Upload PDF file</string>
    	<string name="upload">Upload</string>
    	<string name="select">Select</string>
    	<string name="choose_directory">Choose your file</string>
    	<string name="pdf_error">Selected file is not a PDF file</string>
    	<string name="path_error">There was an error with folders</string>
    	<string name="uploading">Uploading file</string>
    	    	    	    	
    	<!-- Menú contextual -->
    	<string name="select_all">Select all</string>
    	<string name="select_none">Deselect all</string>
    	<string name="title">Select scores</string>
    	<string name="subtitle">1 score selected</string>
    	<string name="subtitle2">scores selected</string>
    	<string name="successDelete">Files deleted successfully</string>
   	<string name="failDelete">An error occurred and we were unable to eliminate 
     selected files</string>
    
    <!-- Pantalla partitura -->
    <string name="metronome">Metronome</string>	
    	<string name="metronome_pause">Pause</string>
    	<string name="metronome_stop">Stop</string>
    	<string name="metronome_play">Play</string>
    	<string name="metronome_back">Back to top</string>
    	<string name="close_metronome">Close metronome</string>
    	<string name="tempo">Tempo</string>
        <string name="score">Scores</string>
    	<string name="speed_allowed">Min. Speed: 1 bpm. Max Speed: 300 bpm.</string>
    	
    <!-- Pantalla panorámica -->
    <string name="panoramic_view">Panoramic</string>
    <string name="vertical_view">Vertical</string>
    	
    <!-- Leer micrófono -->
    <string name="readMicrophone">Microphone</string>
    <string name="microphone_sensitivity">Sensitivity</string>
    <string name="microphone_speed">Speed</string>
    <string name="microphone_start">Start</string>
    <string name="microphone_stop">Stop</string>
    <string name="startPlaying">You can start to play</string>
    <string name="setSensitivity">Adjust sensitivity</string>
    <string name="setSpeed">Adjust speed</string>
    <string name="sensitivityText">
        Adjust the sensitivity of the microphone. \n
	       \t\t -If the value is too low, you will have to play very loud so the application hear you  \n
	       \t\t -If this value is too high, the background noise may interfere with the application and hinder you. \n
	        Searching for an appropriate value that allows you to play comfortably.
    </string>
    <string name="sensitivityButton">Adjust</string>
    <string name="speedText">
        Set the speed at which samples are collected by the microphone.\n\n
		Set this value if you think the score is moving too slowly or too fast.	    
    </string>
    
    <!-- Navegación -->
    <string name="navigate">Navigation</string>
    <string name="navigate_top">Go to the top</string>
    <string name="navigate_bottom">Go to the bottom</string>
    <string name="navigate_to_bar">Go to bar&#8230;</string>
    <string name="number_of_bar">Number of bar</string>
    <string name="go_to_bar">Go to bar</string>
    <string name="wrong_bar_number">There is no bar with that number</string>
    	
    <string name="contentDescription">Image</string>

    <!-- Menú principal contextual -->
    <string name="mis_datos">My profile</string>
    	<string name="mis_datos_nombre">Name:</string>
    	<string name="mis_datos_email">Email:</string>
    	<string name="mis_datos_clave">Change password</string>
    	<string name="mis_datos_clave_vieja">Old password</string>
    	<string name="mis_datos_clave_nueva">New password</string>
    	<string name="mis_datos_clave_repetir">Confirm new password</string>
    	<string name="mis_datos_boton">Change password</string>
    	<string name="mis_datos_clave_cambiada">You password have been change</string>
    	<string name="mis_datos_error_verif">We couldn\'t verify your identity</string>
    	<string name="mis_datos_clave_erronea">Incorrect password</string>
    	<string name="mis_datos_saldo">Credit:</string>
    	<string name="try_change_pass">Trying to change your password. Please wait&#8230;</string>
    	<string name="err_close_session">An error have occurred with signout</string>
    
    <string name="feedback">Feedback</string>
    	<string name="feedback_envianos">
		Send us those errors you\'ve found or suggestions you may have
     		to improve implementation. Thank you very much.
    	</string>
    	<string name="feedback_boton">Send feedback</string>
    	<string name="feedback_enviado">Feedback sent. Thank you for helping us to improve.</string>
    	<string name="sending_feedback">Sending feedback&#8230;</string>
    
    <string name="terminos_condiciones">Terms and conditions</string>
    	<string name="terminos">
    	    TERMS OF USE OF THE APPLICATION\n\n;

			1. ACCEPTANCE OF CONDITIONS OF USE\n\n

			When you install the APPLICATION, you accept the terms of use.\n\n

			2. DEFINITION\n\n

			2.1. The APPLICATION offers to the user access to an online store (hereinafter SHOP) 
			from which the user can acquire at the price given in the SHOP, existing in the catalog 
			offered by RISING scores. You may download scores you purchased on your device and 
			can be used in two ways: by moving them manually or by selecting a metronome speed 
			from which the score will automatically move throughout the piece.\n\n

			2.2. The APPLICATIOM is distributed for free. In addition, RISING will publish
			APPLICATION periodic updates that not accrue any cost to the user.\n\n

			3. DATA PROTECTION\n\n

			Any personal information provided to RISING while using the APPLICATION only be 
			used in accordance with the Privacy Policy RISING.\n\n

			4. LICENSE AND COPYRIGHT\n\n

			4.1. All trademarks, copyrights, database rights and other APPLICATION intellectual 
			property, whatever its nature, as the source code are property of RISING.\n\n

			4.2. Hereby RISING offers a revocable, free, nonexclusive and international licence 
			to use this APPLICATION on a personal or professional level within the limits set by these 
			conditions.\n\n

			5. TERMS OF USE\n\n

			5.1. The user will not act or allow third parties acting on their behalf to:\n\n

				a) Make and distribute copies of the APPLICATION. \n\n
				b) Attempting to copy, reproduce, alter, modify, reverse engineer, disassemble,
				decompile, transfer, exchange or translate APPLICATION. \n\n
				c) Create any kind of project derived from the APPLICATION. \n\n

			5.2. The application provides the user free for personal use and not commercial. 
			RISING reserves the right to modify or disable the APPLICATION any time for any 
			reason. \n\n

			5.3. You agree that the terms of the agreement with the vendor of your mobile network
			("Mobile Service Provider") will continue to apply for the use of the APPLICATION.
			Accordingly, the Supplier may charge for Mobile Services services
			connection to the network while the APPLICATION remain connected to the network, or that
			produce economic positions of others. The user accepts the responsibility of
			charges that may arise. \n\n

			5.4. If the user is not the owner\'s billing phone or mobile device used to access to the 
			APPLICATION, will assume that you have permission from the owner to use the APPLICATION. \n\n

			6. AVAILABILITY\n\n

			6.1. The application is available for mobile handheld devices operating with Android OS operating 
			systems. RISING will make all reasonable efforts to APPLICATION is available at all time. However, 
			you agree that the APPLICATION delivery will be made through internet and mobile networks and,
			therefore, the quality and availability of the APPLICATIOM can be affected by factors beyond the control
			responsible of RISING. \n\n

			6.2. To use the APPLICATION, the user must have a compatible mobile device with internet access 
			and meets the minimum specifications ("Software Requirements"). \n\n

			6.3. The software requirements are: OS Android Devices over 7 inches and the Android OS 4.1 to OS 4.4 
			operating systems. Languages: On devices with languages ​​not supported by the APPLICATION, this will 
			be show in English. \n\n

			7. ACCOUNT DELETING\n\n

			3.2.7.1. You are permitted to terminate your account at any time through tool offered in the 
			APPLICATION for this purpose, and without pre notice to RISING. \ n \ n

			3.2.7.2. The account deletion by the user is an irreversible process that has result in the removal of all 
			user information contained in the RISING database. This information includes the record of purchases 
			made ​​by the user in the STORE. However, the scores that the user has downloaded to the device
			have been acquired through the STORE not be removed from the device, but the user
			must create a new account if want to use. \n\n

			3.2.7.3. The account deletion by the user results in loss of balance that had accumulated in your account, 
			as well as the end of their contractual relationship with RISING. \n\n

			8. TERMINATION\n\n

			8.1. RISING may terminate the use of the APPLICATION at any time, previous notice, which will be published on 
			the BLOG. \n\n

			8.2. At the end of such use, shall also order all rights and licenses granted to the user, which means that the user 
			must stop using the software. \n\n
    	</string>
    
    <string name="condiciones_compra">Term of purchase</string>
    	<string name="condiciones">
    	    TERMS OF PURCHASE\n\n

			1. PURPOSE AND DESCRIPTION OF PRODUCTS\n\n

			RISING S.C.P. (hereinafter RISING) is the creator and owner of the application Scores
			(hereinafter, the APPLICATION) offered on the site www.scores.rising.es (hereinafter, the WEB)
			generated and structured from software, design and content, along with other information
			both own from reputable suppliers and offers online support (hereinafter STORE) 
			in which the CUSTOMER can purchase sheet music in digital format
			that can be used by the application itself. This Agreement regulates the provision and
			supply to the CUSTOMER through the Internet telecommunications network, products
			by RISING. The products are those that are available through the STORE and
			in price lists contained in it, reserving however that company the right
			to amend and revise such rates and products. \n\n

			2. GENERAL TERMS\n\n

			The order by the CUSTOMER of the products of the STORE presupposes the acceptance of these
			Conditions of Purchase and Terms listed both in the  WEB  and in the APPLICATION, and is
			perfected in the moment of the purchase order. \n\n

			The presentation of products on the screen itself does not constitute an offer of sale itself from a
			contractual point of view, but it is merely a showcase of the products available to the STORE. \n\n

			3. PRICE\n\n

			The cost of the products specified in the STORE will be established for each of them and force in
			each time, which is accessible via the store and displayed on the information attached to the product.
			RISING reserves the right to change prices at any time, being of application that modification to the 
			parties since it is incorporated into the Web. \n\n

			4. ACQUISITION OF CREDIT\n\n

			4.1. To purchase any of the products available through the SHOP, the CLIENT will available in the STORE 
			an option that will allow to add credit to the CLIENT\'s account. \n\n

			4.2. This option will consist that the CLIENT  shall pay to RISING a monetary amount that, after payment, will be 
			posted to the CLIENT account as a virtual credit (hereinafter CREDIT). This is the CREDIT
			that allow the CUSTOMER to purchase scores in the STORE. \n\n

			4.3. If the CLIENT does not have enough CRDIT to purchase a score, can not buy it.
			In this case, if the CLIENT wish to acquire this score should add more CREDIT into the account. \n\n

			4.4. RISING don\'t handlecCREDIT returns.\n\n

			5. DELIVERY\n\n

			The delivery of products purchased will occur immediately after the payment has been made and 
			from the STORE. Additionally, an email will be sent to the client with information of the purchase, 
			as well as the bill itself \n\n

			6. RETURNS\n\n

			Being products and services in digital format and for obvious reasons, no returns allowed. \n\n

			7. WARRANTY\n\n

			In the case of a problem, the purchased product could not be downloaded or was technically defective
			so it was impossible to read and use, the CLIENT must contact, before 15 days, with 
			RISING (info@rising.es) to request a copy of these products. RISING provide copies of such
			products provided only if the claim occurs within the 15 days mentioned. \n\n

			In case of loss or corruption of the acquired and paid files in the STORE, RISING provide a new copy
			the CLIENT and will do up to 3 times as long as the product acquired for the CLIENT is current and not 
			discontinued at the time of the application result. To make this possible delivery, the CLIENT must
			contact with RISING and provide necessary information how to both product and verification
			that this was actually purchased in the STORE. \n\n

			8. BILLING AND PAYMENT\n\n

			The CLIENT will make payment of products using the payment gateway enabled by RISING and managed by an
			specialized entity. Payment is made on a secure server. At the time of payment, RISING emits and sends the bill
			to the email address provided by the CLIENT. For security reasons, RISING does not store data of payment in 
			any form, leaving the entire purchase process by the entity. RISING just received, by the entity, the authorization 
			code or failing the cause of failure of the operation (card denied, expired, etc..). \n\n

			9. JURISDICTION AND APPLICABLE LAW\n\n

			9.1. The present Terms shall be governed by the provisions of Spanish legislation.\n\n

			9.2. In the case that any discrepancy or dispute arising from the interpretation or Application of these 
			Terms of Use, RISING and the CLIENT expressly waiving any other jurisdiction he could be entitled, 
			subject to the jurisdiction of the Courts and Tribunals of RISING address. And in the case that the CLIENT is 
			resident outside of Spain, RISING and CLIENT expressly waive any other jurisdiction that may apply, 
			subject to the jurisdiction of the Courts of Las Palmas de Gran Canaria. \n\n    	    
    	</string>

    <string name="cambiar_pass">Change password</string>	
    	
    <string name="eliminar_cuenta">Delete account</string>
    	<string name="esta_seguro">
    	    Are you sure you want to delete your account? If you do it,
     you will lose the credit associated with your account. This operation is irreversible.
     If you still wish to continue, enter your password.
    	</string>
    	<string name="esta_seguro_facebook">
	Are you sure you want to delete your account? If you do it,
     you will lose the credit associated with your account. This operation is irreversible.
    	</string>
    	<string name="error_eliminar_cuenta">
    	   There was an error and could not remove your account. You can try again later.
    	</string>
    	<string name="error_eliminar_cuenta_datos">Error, incorrect data</string>
    	<string name="error_eliminar_cuenta_identidad">
    	    We were unable to verify your identity securely. The operation has been canceled.
    	</string>
    	<string name="error_eliminar_cuenta_fallo_verif">
    	   We were unable to verify this account. The operation has been canceled.
    	</string>
    	<string name="cuenta_eliminada">Your account have been delete successfully.</string>
    	<string name="eliminando_cuenta">Deleting account&#8230;</string>
    	<string name="eliminar_cuenta_clave">Password</string>
    	<string name="yes">Yes</string>
    	<string name="no">No</string>
    	
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    	
    <string name="about">About Scores</string>
	    <string name="version">Version: Beta</string>
	    <string name="acerca_de">Scores is develop by RISING S.C.P.</string>	
	    <string name="visitanos">Visit our site: </string>
    	<string name="web">scores.rising.es</string>
    	<string name="metronome_image_credit">
    	    Metronome icon: made by Icons-land (http://www.icons-land.com)
    	</string>

    <!-- Pantalla tienda -->
    	<string name="store">Store</string>
    	<string name="masinfo">+ Info</string>
    	<string name="pleasewait">Please, wait&#8230;</string>
    	<string name="free">Free</string>
    	<string name="download">Download</string>
    	<string name="coin">€</string>
    	<string name="update">Update</string>
    	<string name="store_error">The store is not available right now. Try again later.</string>
    	<string name="retry">Retry</string>
    	<string name="guitar">Guitar</string>
    	<string name="piano">Piano</string>
    	<string name="quest">Quest</string>
    	<string name="okdownload">The score was downloaded successfully</string>
    	<string name="errordownload">Failed to download the score</string>
    	<string name="error_store">Network failed!</string>
    	<string name="buy_agree">Want to buy this score?</string>
    	<string name="confirm_buy">Confirm purchase</string>
    	<string name="buy">Buy</string>
    	<string name="not_enough_credit">Insufficient credit</string>
    	<string name="no_money">You do not have enough credit to make the purchase. </string>
    	<string name="buy_credit">Buy credit</string>
    	<string name="open">Open</string>
    	<string name="downloading">Downloading</string>
    	<string name="win_buy">You have received 0,01 credit!</string>
    	<string name="no_space">You haven\'t got space enough in your device</string>
    	<string name="my_purchases">My purchases</string>
    	    	
    		<!-- Pantalla busqueda -->
    		<string name="list">List</string>
    		<string name="empty_result">No scores were found</string>
    		<string name="searching">Searching&#8230;</string>
    		
    		<!-- Pantalla saldo -->
    		
    			<!-- Pantalla compra dinero -->
	    			<string name="money">Credit</string>
		    		<string name="current_money">Current credit:  </string>
		    		<string name="free_money">Get free credit!</string>
		    		<string name="add5">Add 5 credits</string>
		    		<string name="add10">Add 10 credits + 1 Free</string>
		    		<string name="add20">Add 20 credits + 2 Free</string>
		    		<string name="add50">Add 50 credits + 5 Free</string>
		    		<string name="add100">Add 100 credits + 10 Free</string>
		    		<string name="google_init_error">Fail to init the comunication with Google</string>
		    		<string name="buy_fail">Fail to finish the purchase. This didn\'t do it</string>
		    		<string name="buy_fail2">Fail to register the purchase</string>
		    		<string name="buy_ok">The purchase was successed</string>

	    		<!-- Pantalla saldo gratis -->
    				<string name="share_friends">Share with friends</string>
    				<string name="share_social">Share in social networks</string>
    				<string name="share_button">Share</string>
    				<string name="share_friends_text">Invite your friends to join to Scores</string>
    				<string name="share_social_text">Share how much you like Scores in social networks</string>
    				<string name="friendmail">Enter a friend e-mail</string>
    				<string name="friendmail_empty">This field cannot be empty</string>
			    	<string name="friendmail2">Friend e-mail</string>
			    	<string name="receive_friends">You will receive 0,15 credits!</string>
			    	<string name="receive_social">You will receive 0,05 credits!</string>
			    	<string name="rate_app">Rate Scores on Google Play Store</string>
			    	<string name="receive_rate">You will receive 0,05 credits!</string>
			    	<string name="win_social">You have received 0,05 credits!</string>
			    	<string name="fail_social">Fail to register your share</string>
			    	<string name="share_rate">Rate the app</string>
			    	<string name="wait">You should wait </string>
			    	<string name="hours"> hours to post again</string>
			    	<string name="tweet_done">Tweet sent successfully</string>
			    	<string name="tweet_fail">There was an error and could not send the tweet</string>
			    	<string name="fail_market_app">Unable to find market app</string>			    	
    		
    <!-- Pantalla perfil partituras -->
    	<string name="share">Share</string>

    <!-- Pantalla preferencias -->	
    	<string name="user_profile">User profile</string>
    	    	
    <!-- Errores -->
    	<string name="connection_err">An error occurred on the connection</string>
</resources>
